Railroad?
Yes, sir.
So you're saying I could enjoy all my favorite things at the same time?
Yeah, it's so great!
It was really a wonderful Lero-Lero-Journey!
Thank you very much.
Wow!
Wow, wow, wow!
This is great!
Oh, there's some kind of live feed.
Oh, it's so fast!
Wow.
What? They're in, they're saying so suddenly.
So, uh...
That's all for today. See you all tomorrow!
See you all tomorrow!
Yes, OK. Good morning.
So, is it Friday?
Friday 1, right?
It's really nice.
Hey, wow!
Looks like fun!
And, you know, it's so convenient to use the Shinkansen.
Wow!
It's only 40 minutes to Mishima from Shinjuku.
So close!
Wow, wow, wow!
Kodama?
Yes, Kodama.
I love it!
Shizuoka is really great for ekisoba.
Shizuoka's ekisoba fans have been saying for a long time that Shizuoka's level of ekisoba is really good.
I see.
Thank you very much! It's just plain delicious!
I love croquette soba, too. I want to try it again right now.
I heard Mishima is famous for croquettes. Mishima croquettes.
Yes, please.
Yes, I'll go on the air.
Fifty!
Four... three...
Congratulations!
Well, the weekend will be here before you know it.
The weekend?
I had a bit of a shock the other day.
You know...
You know that second hand on a clock?
You know, I haven't seen it much lately.
I haven't seen it much recently.
For the past 10 years or so.
It's not that detailed.
But, on the other hand...
When I'm going about my daily life...
You're the kind of person who counts in your mind
You know, you're the one who counts the seconds in one, two, three, right?
It's been a while since I looked at the second hand properly.
It was a lot faster than I thought it would be.
I thought, "Oh my God.
I've been thinking
I thought it was 10 seconds
I thought it was 10 seconds, but it was like 20 seconds.
Oh my God.
So I guess I'm getting ahead of myself
The times are moving faster than I thought.
That's why.
I don't know.
I don't know... in terms of... in terms of the world...
In the world
You're all saying "Take it away!
You're saying it!
I'm dancing, dancing, dancing.
Teik-tak-tak!
That was a bit of a shock to me.
You know...
Well, that's the way it is.
I'll get right to it.
Let's see...
What's going on? There's some kind of bug around here.
I'm working on it. It's not a bug.
I'm Sakurai Sakurai.
I'm Sakurai. Meiji, it's cancer.
I'm a little nervous when you say "cancer." I'm Gandari.
So, let's start with a word of wisdom.
This is...
Yamaha is famous as a manufacturer of musical instruments and motorcycles.
The founder of Yamaha is said to be Yamaha Trucks.
He was a long time ago, and there are only a few old photos of him left.
I saw a little bit of him, but he looks like this, Mr. Yamaha Trucks.
He looks like a musician. He was born in Wakayama Prefecture in 1851, in the Edo period.
Edo period? 1916 is the Taisho Era. He built Japan's first organ and piano.
He made Japan's first organ and piano.
When I first heard "Mr. Trakus", I thought he was from overseas.
Yamaha is famous for its guitars and so on.
Yamaha is famous for guitars, too, but I didn't know they'd been around this long.
I didn't know it had been around for so long.
I didn't realize that Yamaha has been around for so long.
May I?
A man can't succeed in business unless he's in love with a man.
That's a good quote.
I see. This is especially true for men.
It's true... even those who work with them.Sure, there are people I work with, people who are my subordinates, but...
Of course, there are many men who ride the instruments and bikes that I made.
Of course, there are many men who ride my instruments and bikes.
You have to keep on winning the hearts of those people.
If they don't fall in love with you...
It's not easy, but it's quite common for a guy to fall in love with another guy, isn't it?
I want to be like that. I'm going to have to work harder.
97% of my fans are women. Only about 3% are men.
But there are still some.
I'd like to work hard on the men's business.
I'm okay with this kind of person.
What do you think?
I think you're fine like this.
Then leave it as it is.
I think of a man who can make a man fall in love with him as a lucky guy.
But I don't think that's all it is.
I see.
Of course.
That's why Mr. Yamaha made his statement.
What day is tomorrow?
Tomorrow is finally Saturday!
It's finally July!
Is that applause?
July 1st is... the "Yama-biraki" or the "opening of the mountain".
The opening of the mountains?
Mountains all over Japan open from today.
Of course, there are places where you can climb even before that. Yes, yes, yes, yes. Basically, the mountain opens on July 1.
It is already July. It's already July. Like I said before, we've created a lot more time than I thought. That's right.
It feels even faster. I still feel like it's March 18th. I feel like it's March 18th. Yes, yes. It's already June. Already almost doubled.
It's gone up like this, hasn't it? Second hand. It's like, "Wow.
I thought it might be broken.
So I checked it again with a stopwatch on my cell phone or something.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, no!
It's too early!
I want you all to be careful
Please be careful.
Where?
No, no, no, I mean... if you're taking it easy like that...
It'll be over soon.
That's right.
Until a year from now.
And now... let's hear from you.
Let's hear from some of you. Thank you, Ms. Tamami, from Tokyo. This is the person who always sends me pictures of books.
Painter. Master Ebichu-chan, Sawapon-kun, Komban Devil Master Hoshina-san and Sawapon-kun in the live delivery the other day.
How are you today? How are you doing today?
Yeah, yeah, it's kind of...
No, no, no, no, no!
I taught you well!
I taught it to Sanjay.
I did it, but in the end, it was just me.
I was the only one who did it, and it was the other way around.
Oh, yeah!
That's right!
This one.
It says it's from the delivery.
Hey!
But you know what?
You think it's the other way around.
Yes, I do.
No, what I'm saying is...
These people, they represent the cression.
I mean, that's what the French C stands for. The C for "sa," the C for "mackerel.
Oh, that's the one. Oh, right. You guys have the cression mark. It's French.
Oh, hey, so it's a little bit dimensional. Give me a break.
Don't paint it out again.
Scary, scary, scary.
I cracked my ear today.
Why? My ear cracked today.
My ear is cracked. Thank you very much.
So, I mentioned Yamanami earlier... Yamanami is based in Hamamatsu, Shizuoka.
And the person who happened to go there is Ms. Yukisara from Yokohama City Minami Ward.
Thank you very much for your letter.
There is a service area in Hamamatsu on the way to the highway, and as expected in Hamamatsu, there are musical instruments and drums, and anyone can play street drums while taking a break.
It's amazing that it's in a service area.
Oh, how nice!
This must be a drama.
Is it an electronic drama? As expected, that live one is a bit noisy.
I'm sure it's going to be like that, but... Wow, that sounds like fun!
Hamamatsu is also the home of a musical instrument company.
There's a lot of factories there, too.
Yes, and this is interesting, too.
Sirenus from Mishima City, Shizuoka Prefecture.
The other day, I participated in a workshop where you can try on armor.
Yes, me?
You know, the one that's on the 643rd?
That's armor, isn't it?
And that European silver armor...
And the guy with the silver armor...
This is really cool armor!
armor looks heavy... armor is heavy... armor is heavy... real armor... real armor... really heavy... armor is really heavy...
Armor...
It's a replica, but it's so heavy that it made me wonder how people used to fight with such inconvenient things.
I love the Warring States period, and I've talked to many experts and enthusiasts about it.
I've talked to many experts and enthusiasts, and they often show battle scenes in which people are wearing armor and swords, and they get cut by a sword and fall down, you know?
They say that doesn't happen often.
Armor is colored, so it's not so easy to be cut by a sword.
Most of the time, there's a little gap between the parts of the armor, and then a spear or a sword is inserted into the gap, and then the armor is cut.
There wasn't that kind of bishon-dosa feeling, like, "Oh, no, don't do that, don't do that, don't do that.
And also the sword to sword... I have to show the drama...
Basher!Basher!
It's almost impossible for a sword to fall down with a thud, right?
It's mostly the weight of the sword.
Boom, boom, boom, boom!
It doesn't cut that fast.
It's not that easy.
So, the weight of the sword makes a big thud...
And then, "Ora!
It wasn't like that.
I heard it was terrible.
The side and the other... Wow!
He hit the most painful part.
Oh, no.
That's horrible.
Oh, no!
I know everyone's saying that, but...
It really hurts, it really hurts, it really hurts.
You're hurting, you're hurting, you're hurting, you're hurting.
Stop it, stop it.
I think that's what he was obsessed with on the battlefield.
That's about it.
It was influenced by historical dramas and tiger dramas.
It's like they're really good at it.
I have an image of a warlord on a horse cutting off the enemy's head in a flash, right?
It's almost impossible for that to happen.
So it's a pitched battle?
Not really... it's normal.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
Well, well, well...
And...
Cervone, too.
One photo. This is a mysterious picture. What is this?
This is a vocabulary test that my guesser was doing a while ago.
Vocabulary test?
Yes. It was a vocabulary test to see how good your vocabulary was.
I don't know how much vocabulary I have.
There were various kanji characters and you had to choose 4 options to find out what they meant. Like a real test. Oh, yes, that's right.
I was wondering what my vocabulary was like by doing that. Yes, that's right. You're an 18-year-old teenager.
What does that mean? I have the same vocabulary as an 18-year-old teenager. Well, 18 years old is a pretty good age, isn't it?
Yes, it is. Like a high school student. Oh, so it's like your vocabulary improves as you get older?
I thought so. I think that's probably true. But I was surprised to see that you are in the top 24%.
What?
That's right. But I thought I'd like you all to give it a try.
I think I'm probably in the top 2%.
But it sure looks amazing.
So does Emma.
Can you please be quiet? What are you talking about?
I've been here for a while now.
Your sins, your sins, your sins. We took it and we're still alive. Get up, again.
The person in charge says he can go on. What is going on here? What's going on here?
What? What is the bottom of this? I think it's already a baby or something.
By the way, for example, let's say I remember something.
What?
It was a while ago. I did it a while ago. What? Sounds interesting. By the way, do you think this will show up? Maybe I can look it up around here. It's a language proficiency test.
What's that? Alias me. Language Proficiency Test, maybe on safari. Just one question.
Was it difficult? No, it was pretty difficult. I thought I could understand it surprisingly well, but there were some difficult ones. 24 is amazing, isn't it? Surprisingly.
How about the 18th?
Is it this one? Oh, I think that's it. That's it, that's it, that's it.
Have you ever wondered how big your vocabulary is? Yes, I have.
I think it's fine on a day like this. It's a good day for me.
It's like being an announcer.
You use Japanese every day, or Japanese is...
You might find this test difficult even if it's in your native language.
I see.
By doing our own academic research and looking at online information, we have prepared a very good test that you will not find on this quiz.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Start measuring...
Oh, that's it.
No, it's not good.
By the way, learn! Synonyms for.
Synonyms.
I'll learn.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay? This is learn.
Oh.
Yes.
I see.
Oh, ha-ha-ha.
What is a synonym for serious?
Serious. Oh.
Synonym for warm. Yes.
Compassionate. There are so many problems with this.
Really? Yes. Then, let's have them try not to work too hard. Yes, that's right.
Okay. The last one. Last? Last synonym.
Here. The end? The end. Oh, you're probably right. Yeah.
Imaginary synonyms. I think.
Certainly. There are. Synonyms for
Receive.
Woooiii! Huh? Surprising! Wait a minute, sorry!
You're doing great! I thought I was the one who was gonna get it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, you're good! You're good!
That's awesome!
Wait a minute.
You scared me. By the way, what is a synonym for trust?
Trust.
That's right. That's probably right.
What is a synonym for negative?
I don't know. I don't know.
Negative? Exclusive?Passive? Exclusive?
This is probably not. This is probably passive. What's that?
Like this. That's right. If you do this more and more, you'll find out how good you are. How many questions do you have?
There were quite a few. I think it's not more than 50 questions. About? I think. How many of them? How many of them did Saab get right?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. It just seems like this is the number that comes up. It's okay. Please give it a try.
Well, there are a lot of these things these days, aren't there? Yes, there are. Like the MBTI test.
This one too. It's big. Is it the other way around? Small.
Wow, it's really long. Hard. Soft. Beginning. Ends.
The unexpected kind. Unexpected? Unexpected.
A synonym for cold. Hot.
The synonym for true or sincere is false. It is said to take true and false. Superior, gentle The synonym for superior is take.
The synonym for natural is artificial. The synonym for human tone is thoughtless.
The synonym for yesterday is yesterday? Yesterday? Yesterday?
What? Yesterday, not yesterday? Yesterday? Maybe. Yesterday. Maybe it was yesterday.
What? What is this? Is this really right?
Is this the right question? It reads wrong.
And what's this? I've never seen a circle something like this before. I'm sure.
Function. Function.
There are only two, right? In yesterday's words, the function of functional. Functional.
Synonym for surface dense.
Up-to-date.
Synonyms for developmental.
Progress.
Disadvantages Synonyms.
It's time for a complete horse meal.
It is coming.
Empire.
There's more!
Synonymous synonyms.
But maybe there's a little more to come.
Synonyms.
Hang in there.
Synonym.
Yes.
Will of the people.
Yoron.
It's anti-difference time.
The will of the people.
Ethics.
Ah, it works.
Organization.
It's also written "return," "govern," and "function.
And function it does!
Wow, amazing!
What a genius!
Yes, it is.
Organization.
Wow.
Tissue synonym.
You work too many shifts, don't you? I've been told.
I'm working.
Because we need the money.
Hand.
Synonyms for skill.
Skill.
There's more, light sword.
It's quite long, isn't it?
It's quite long.
Light sword, dexterity.
It might be almost there.
A synonym for just.
Injustice.
Mm-hmm.
Synonym for bare edge.
No, that's a long one.
Bare relationship, intimate.
Synonym for lawless.
Imagination. Synonym for wasteful.
Ehhhh! Contract. Synonym for ailment.
Chairman! Synonyms for kind.
Kindness. Cold-heartedness.
Yes, indifferent.
What's a decision?
This is probably until it's maxed out.
Eeeee! What the hell! Hey!
Please do your best!
DECISION.
I'll give you a decision.
I'll see if I can't do my best
I've got to go!
You're patsy-cute
Hey, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
I'll tell you later
Well, well, well, well.
I'll tell you the result later.
That's all I have to say.
Well, you know... today was mostly...
It's like a study time.
That's right.
Well, what I learned this time is...
Surprisingly, your grades in school aren't so bad.
I see.
Not so good at school, though.
School's not good?
He's being bounced to the side of the school.
That was really fast.It was crazy fast.
I might have a vocabulary.
I'm sure you do have a vocabulary.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Also, if the school had some kind of class on "aiite" or something...
I think Ganbatani is great
You know, he's really good at ganbatani ai no te
I see
Like, "Good luck!
Ai's hands are exquisite
I wish she'd put it in.
The timing is so perfect that I'm carried along and end up talking more and more.
That's right.
I would like to see high school students take a class on "Ai-no-Te" every hour, once a week.
Ai-no-Te class
It's important, isn't it?
Well, well, well... that's why I'm here.
By the way...
Well, I'd better get going.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
Something else is coming.
Devil's Charge is here.
Devil's Charge!
Congratulations on the anniversary of Ganbatani's birthday solo!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Please come, by all means
You must be Tamamiyu!
And Hiropaa-san!
Of course I'll come.
That's right.
I'll come if I'm invited.
Please come.
I'll go wherever I'm called.
Even if...
I would never come.
Even if you suddenly ask me to come to Egypt...
Really?
I just said that.
Is that it again?
That place in Yokohama?
There.
Yokohama.
Um...
ZEPP Yokohama.
ZEPP.
Please come.
I'll be by myself.
I'm not worried about singing or anything.
I'm sure you're right.
I'm worried.
I'm really worried, and I'm really looking forward to it.
The MC.
I know, right?
The big comment!
What are you going to do and what are you going to say?
That's right.
I can't do the "ai" move by myself.
I can't speak alone.
I'd be in trouble if I were alone.
That's true.
I'm a professional at making love.
That's not my job.
Maybe that's what you're saying.
But you're right.
Sometimes...
I talk to a lot of people.
The bedrock valley is...
It's like...
Something good.
They all say with sincerity that they're thinking something
Everyone says it with sincerity.
Something like this...
I wonder...
You know, in the entertainment business...
I know, but...
Even if you're good at
Even if you're good at all the technical stuff...
You know...
People who are accepted by everyone...
People who sell well...
A sense of presence...
Just being there...
Just by being there
You know, just being there.
Oh!
What's he doing?
You know, the kind of person that people would look at without thinking
I think the person who will be very successful in this kind of world
I think that's the person who will be very successful in this world.
There are a lot of people in the world who are good at technical things.
Yes, there are.
By all means, keep up the good work.
As it is...
As a magicianAs an Ai no Te Majin
The Hands of the Devil.
What? There's something here.
I just got a huge compliment.
Ai no Te Majin.
It's amazing.
It's Majin-level.
You're on a Majin Boo level?
He's really a Majin Ai no Te Majin.
That's amazing.
Well, well, well...
I'll see you all later.
I'd love to see you all at the nativity.
I'd love to see you.
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
Okay, bye.
See you.
Well, see you.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't mean wow.
You've been on this a lot.
It was closer than I thought.
Closer than I thought.
That's not good either, is it?
I see.
It's surprisingly realistic.
It's very real.
Very much so.
Just like this.
That's it.
You see them in parks all the time.
About the size of a blue Taisho.
Is it that big?
About this big.
It's here, isn't it?
Suddenly...
They come down from above.
Just like that.
When walking in the park...
The green ones fell with a thud.
I thought a tree fell and broke a branch.
Like this.
Wow!
But that blue Taisho.
I don't think this is a Blue Taisho
Ao Taisho never harmed anyone at all.
Ew...
When I pet him like this...
"Hey, hey, hey!
He's so summery!
I'm sorry.
Oh, really?
Like this.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Hunchback...
He's a tough guy.
Don't get carried away.
You're in big trouble.
It's bad, isn't it?
But the Hunchback, you can tell at first sight.
"This guy's a bad guy.
Oh, really?
I said, "This guy's tough.
Here it comes!
Be careful!
That venomous snake is triangular in shape.
Their faces are triangular.
I hear that.
Cobra.
Yes, yes, yes, and cobras, too.
Venomous snakes are like this.
Like this.
So, at first glance...
This one's not so good.
Is it okay to run away with Gunda?
Is it okay to run away with Ganda?
Yes, I'm fine.
Oh, you're sure?
Basically, yes.
If they attack something that's trying to escape...
They never do that.
Really?
Because they're afraid of humans.
They're afraid of humans.
So we have to make contact if at all possible.
But with a bang...
I made contact.
I was afraid of what humans might do to them.
I'm scared.
Don't do it!